<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>文章 on Hoi&#39;s Pages</title>
    <link>http://pages.fadryl.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 文章 on Hoi&#39;s Pages</description>
    <image>
      <url>http://pages.fadryl.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>http://pages.fadryl.com/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 19:37:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://pages.fadryl.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>简历 Résumé</title>
      <link>http://pages.fadryl.com/posts/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 19:37:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pages.fadryl.com/posts/resume/</guid>
      <description>Resume Education Monash University Dec 2021 Bachelor of Computer Science Clayton, VIC, AUS Coursework: Advanced Data Structure and Algorithm; Databases; Modelling for Data Analysis; Big Data Management and Processing; Theory of Computation; Artificial Intelligence; Parallel Computing; Deep Learning.
Monash College OCT 2019 Diploma of Engineering (Information Technology) Clayton, VIC, AUS Coursework: Introduction to Algorithm and Programming; Introduction to Computer System, Networks and Security; Computing for Engineers; Foundations of 3D; Fundamentals of C++.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>隐私权政策 Private Policy</title>
      <link>http://pages.fadryl.com/posts/private-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 19:44:45 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pages.fadryl.com/posts/private-policy/</guid>
      <description>中文 我们不会收集及以任何形式储存来自你社交网络的任何咨询或销售给广告或其它营运机构。
个人信息 当你透过社交网络进行分享时，可能会要求输入账号密码，但该资讯由系统管理，App不会以任何形式储存账号密码，也不会收集及以任何形式储存您在社交网络上的任何个人资讯。
隐私政策条款 使用本App即表示您同意此隐私政策的条款和条件。如果您不同意本政策，请不要使用该App。我们保留权利，在我们決定更改，修改，增加或刪除本政策的部分，在任何時候。请定期浏览此网页查阅任何修改。如果您继续使用我们的App以后的任何更改这些条款的发布将意味着你已经接受了这些调整。
联络邮箱: fadryl@outlook.com
English We do not collect and save from your social account in any form or sell any information to advertisers or other operators.
Personal information When you share information through social accounts may be asked to enter the account and password, but that information is management by the system. App does not save account and password in any form or collect and save any personal information in any form on your social account.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
